<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss xmlns:googleplay="http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:rawvoice="http://www.rawvoice.com/rawvoiceRssModule/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>UCL Christian Union What now? 2021</title>
    <googleplay:author>UCL Christian Union</googleplay:author>
    <itunes:author>UCL Christian Union</itunes:author> 
    <itunes:category text="Religion &amp; Spirituality" />
    <image>
      <url>https://uclchristianunion.github.io/images/main.png</url>
      <title>UCL Christian Union What now? 2021</title>
      <link>https://uclchristianunion.github.io</link>
    </image>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>UCL CU</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>ucl.christianunion@gmail.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:keywords>Christianity,faith</itunes:keywords>
    <copyright>UCL Christian Union 2021</copyright>
    <description><![CDATA[Have you ever achieved something that you were chasing, only to realize it doesn't make you as happy as you thought it would? Have you ever placed your trust in a solution to a problem that did not end up working? Has this pandemic stripped from you things that were important to you? Do you ever just find yourself sitting and thinking... what now? In February 2021, UCL Christian Union hosted events week, which is a series of talks exploring the theme of "What now?" In those moments when we have nothing but the question "what now?" in our heads, is there really no way to find an answer? Whether you call yourself a Christian or not, we would love to invite you to check out this wonderful lineup of talks about a different pressing topic each day.]]></description>
    <googleplay:image href="https://uclchristianunion.github.io/images/main.png" />
    <language>en-en</language>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <link>https://uclchristianunion.github.io/feed.xml</link>
    <itunes:image href="https://uclchristianunion.github.io/images/main.png" />
    <item>
      <itunes:author>UCL Christian Union </itunes:author>
      <title>Success Culture and Christianity - How can i succeed and fail without it ruining me?</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://uclchristianunion.github.io/audio/WhatNow/WhatNowSuccess.mpeg" type="audio/mpeg" length="29512661" />
      <itunes:duration>39:33</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[ We are brought up in a culture that teaches us to succeed. This might mean making good money, getting a good job, making our family proud, getting good grades at uni... So we strive to achieve them. But you feel like an imposter, everyone around you seems better than you are. You’re told to work harder, that a bit more success will make you feel better. But it never does… There's always more, it's overwhelming, the fear of failure, the feeling of insignificance. So… what now? Events week is a series of talks organized by the UCL Christian Union, around 40min each, and this year we are exploring the theme of "What now?". We are very excited to have Peter Dray from UCCF speak to us on the first topic "Success Culture and Christianity - How Can I Succeed And Fail Without It Ruining Me?"<br /><br />---<br /><br />Check out our social media to stay up to date with future events:<br /><br />Facebook: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/uclcu" rel="noopener">https://www.facebook.com/uclcu</a>/​​​​​<br /><br />Instagram: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/ucl.cu/" rel="noopener">https://www.instagram.com/ucl.cu/</a> ]]>
      </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2078770666</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <itunes:author>UCL Christian Union</itunes:author>
      <title><![CDATA[Sex, Relationships & Christianity]]></title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 18:11:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://uclchristianunion.github.io/audio/WhatNow/whatnow2s.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="12854138" />
      <itunes:duration>41:07</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[ Romantic relationships have been an integral part of human life pretty much since the beginning of time. How do contemporary sexual ethics align with Christian teaching? The topic of sex and relationships isn’t very often talked about in relation to Christianity, and when we do we hear about it, it tends to involve controversies around bigotry prejudice. What does the Bible say about all of this? How did God design relationships to work? And is any of this still relevant? So... what now? ]]>
      </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false"> 12089979908 </guid >
     </item>
     <item>
      <itunes:author>UCL Christian Union</itunes:author>
      <title> <![CDATA[Christianity & Environmental responsibility - Climate Crisis: can we save our world?]]>   </title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 18:21:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://uclchristianunion.github.io/audio/WhatNow/whatnow3.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="24845304" />
      <itunes:duration>32:12</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[ Around the world we are experiencing the effect of climate change: water and air temperatures are rising at alarming rates, adversely affecting the habitats that sustain life for fish, animals, plants and human beings. To be fair, most of the responsibility falls on us, exploiting the Earth’s resources to our benefit. And even though we try to be more environmentally friendly as a collective, there doesn’t seem to be as many drastic improvements as we would like. So… what now? ]]>
      </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false"> 12609836250 </guid >
     </item>
     <item>
      <itunes:author>UCL Christian Union</itunes:author>
      <title> <![CDATA[Jesus, Emotions & Mental Health]]>   </title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 18:22:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://uclchristianunion.github.io/audio/WhatNow/whatnow4.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="21214053" />
      <itunes:duration>30:54</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[ ‘Just learn to love yourself’, they say. ‘Just think on the positive side’, they say. ‘Stop complaining because other people have it way worse than you’. So we furrow our brows, and muster up what little strength we have and try to smile. But our struggles are real, your struggles are real… We can try all we want, but sometimes we just don’t seem to have the strength within ourselves. So… what now? ]]>
      </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false"> 52160052823 </guid >
     </item>
     <item>
      <itunes:author>UCL Christian Union</itunes:author>
      <title> <![CDATA[Christ & Justice]]>   </title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 18:23:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://uclchristianunion.github.io/audio/WhatNow/whatnow5s.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="14922219" />
      <itunes:duration>43:03</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[ Everyday there is a lot of injustice happening around the world, including political repression or even people being tortured because of their religious beliefs… It is frustrating and nearly impossible to change many of these by ourselves. What can we do then? Does God really exist, and if he does is he really turning a blind eye towards these things? Does he have the same feelings as us? If so, why hasn't he responded? What is our role if our ability to create change is so limited? So… what now? ]]>
      </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false"> 69949377564 </guid >
     </item>
   <item>
    <itunes:author>UCL Christian Union</itunes:author>
    <title> <![CDATA[Why Christianity over another religion?]]>   </title>
    <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 14:06:53 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://uclchristianunion.github.io/audio/WhatNow/fritalk1 (audio-extractor.net).mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="12219906" />
    <itunes:duration>24:08</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <description>
      <![CDATA[ This is the first of our series of four lunch talks following Events Week! Join us as we hear from Michael Williams from the UCCF Theology Network about the topic: "Why Christianity over another religion?" ]]>
    </description>
    <guid isPermaLink="false"> 32566707806 </guid >
   </item>
   <item>
    <itunes:author>UCL Christian Union</itunes:author>
    <title> <![CDATA[What is the point in the Bible?]]>   </title>
    <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 14:24:22 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://uclchristianunion.github.io/audio/WhatNow/fritalk2.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="13006974" />
    <itunes:duration>23:47</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <description>
      <![CDATA[ Christians talk about reading the Bible all the time. But what is it about the Bible that makes it so special? What even is the point in reading this book that was written so long ago? Can I be a Christian without having to read the Bible? Join us as we hear from Giles Cattermole from UCCF about this topic! ]]>
    </description>
    <guid isPermaLink="false"> 30625811371 </guid >
   </item>
   <item>
    <itunes:author>UCL Christian Union</itunes:author>
    <title> <![CDATA[Who is Jesus]]>   </title>
    <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 14:30:08 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://uclchristianunion.github.io/audio/WhatNow/fritalk3.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="18975497" />
    <itunes:duration>35:59</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <description>
      <![CDATA[ Perhaps we all associate the name "Jesus" with different things. But who exactly was or is Jesus? Was he actually a real person who walked the Earth? And if so, what relevance does that have with our 21st century lives? Join us as we hear from Tom Kendall from the UCCF Politics Network about this topic! ]]>
    </description>
    <guid isPermaLink="false"> 86734010492 </guid >
   </item>
   <item>
    <itunes:author>UCL Christian Union</itunes:author>
    <title> <![CDATA[Can anyone be forgiven?]]>   </title>
    <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 14:33:42 GMT</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://uclchristianunion.github.io/audio/WhatNow/fritalk4.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="12613462" />
    <itunes:duration>27:51</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <description>
      <![CDATA[ Christians talk about a merciful God who forgives our sins, but does that mean that everyone, regardless of what they have done, can be forgiven? How is it possible that God is both merciful and just? Join us as we hear from our UCCF staff worker Connor Perring about this topic! ]]>
    </description>
    <guid isPermaLink="false"> 10281497169 </guid >
   </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
